I run a dietitian consulting and wellness services company.
We did three point five million in revenue in twenty twenty five.
I'd like to be a ten million in revenue.
I definitely have those visions, a hundred million dollar models.
And I think the thing that I struggle with is I get so excited
about the different models that I struggle to say no to the right things
and say yes to the right things.
Is there a framework you utilize to be more decisive in your yeses and nos?
Keith Cunningham is a really good thought process for this,
which is what's the upside?
Number one, what's the downside?
And can I live with the downside?
And if the downside is not livable, then you just don't do it.